W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1916-1981, undated; 2
  - Department of Commerce, 1931-1979, undated; 2
    - Patent Office, Trademark Rules, circa 1955 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Patents, Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Presidential Veto, Norwich University, 1945 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1962-1966 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Press Releases, 1974-1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Maritime Commission (MARCOM), “Analysis of Construction and Operating Subsidies”, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Merchant Marines, Application Materials, 1953, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Weather Service Office, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - World Trade Week, Printed Materials, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Department of Defense, 1936-1978, undated; 3
    Subseries III, one of the largest in Series II. Departments, contains materials pertaining to the Department of Defense. There is a significant amount of correspondence from each branch of the military, particularly covering the years of American involvement in the Vietnam War. Another major section of the subseries contains reports and publications from the Army Corps of Engineers and projects they conducted in Central Texas including ones on the Brazos River and Lake Whitney. Other topics addressed include ones of local interest such as Doris Miller, Connally Air Force Base, and Fort Hood.
    Many materials were deaccessioned from this subseries. These included personal casefiles, applications to the various military academies, correspondence concerning orders, and requests to Bob Poage to facilitate transfers or discharges.
    Note that materials on the Coast Guard can be found under the Department of Treasury (pre-1967) and the Department of Transportation (post-1967).
    Folders in this subseries are divided alphabetically by branch of military when possible. There are also materials relating to the Department of Defense in general which are typically identified by material type. Most of the materials in this subseries are in good condition.
    - Air Force, Air Force Academy, Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Air Force, Air Force Academy, Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Air Force, Air Force Academy, Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Air Force, Air Force Academy, Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Air Force, Air Force Academy, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1950-1952 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1953-1954 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1955-1956 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1957-1959 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1962-1964 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1965-1968 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1969-1970 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1973-1975 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Air Force, Correspondence, General, 1976-1978 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Air Force, James Connally Air Force Base Closure, Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Air Force, James Connally Air Force Base Closure, Legislative Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Air Force, McGregor Auxiliary Airfield, Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Air Force, Spying in Iceland, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Air Force, Taylor Moving and Storage Company, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Air Force, Wool Clothing, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Americans Unaccounted for in Southeast Asia, Memos and Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Announcements, 1971-1978 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Army, A.O. Smith Corporation, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1965-1969 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Belton Lake, Congressional Inquiry (1 of 3), 1971-1977 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Belton Lake, Congressional Inquiry (2 of 3), 1971-1977 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Belton Lake, Congressional Inquiry (3 of 3), 1971-1977 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Booklet, “Water Resources Development by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers”, 1967 January (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Booklet, “Water Resources Development by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers”, 1969 January (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Booklet, “Water Resources Development”, 1977 January (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Civil Works Program, Budget Report, 1967 November (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Civil Works Program, Budget Report, 1969 January (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Civil Works Program, Budget Report, 1972 August (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Civil Works Program, Budget Report, 1976 July (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Civil Works Program, Budget Report, Fiscal Year 1979, 1978 January (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Lake Whitney Management Regulations, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Maps, 1955-1969, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Navigability of Brazos River, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, “Operation and Maintenance Environmental Statement: Belton Lake, Texas”, 1973 February (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Press Releases, 1968-1973 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Printed Materials and Reports, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Printed Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Printed Materials and Statements, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Printed Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Public Notices, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Recreation Fees at Lakes, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Water Reservoirs, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Water Reservoirs, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Water Reservoirs, Press Releases and Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Water Reservoirs, Printed Materials, 1971-1977 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Army, Army Corps of Engineers, Watershed Projects, Report, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1952 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1955 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1959 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Army, Correspondence, General, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Army, Deployment Criteria, Correspondence, 1974 June 24 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Army, Fort Bliss El Paso Military Civilian Community, Fact Book, 1978 March (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Army, Fort Hood, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Army, Press Releases, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Army, Report, “Inside the United States Continental Army Command (First Army)”, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Army, Reserve Officers’ Training Corps, Pamphlet, Scholarships, 1973 December (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Army, Reserve Officers’ Training Corps, Printed Materials, 1978, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Army, Reserve Officers’ Training Corps, Report, Scholarship Awards, 1974 March 29 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Army, Texas Agencies, Clippings and Printed Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Army, Texas Agencies, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Army, Texas Bandmasters Association, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Army, “The Army’s Master Program for the Modern Volunteer Army”, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Army, West Point, Correspondence, 1936-1953 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Army, West Point, Correspondence, 1954-1969 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Army, West Point, Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Army, West Point, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Army, Volunteer Army, Report, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Army, Year-End Report, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Army-National Guard, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Army-Navy Football Game, Ticket Information, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - B-1 Bomber, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Bicentennial, Armed Forces Exhibit Vans Project, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Child Support and Alimony, Memorandum, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Civil Air Patrol (CAP), Annual Report to Congress, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Civil Defense, Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Civil Service Commission Exam, Printed Materials, 1972-1976, undated (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Civilian Health and Medical Program of the Uniformed Services (CHAMPUS), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1974-1976 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Commissaries, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - “Congressional Guide for Admissions: Tri-Service Academies”, 1973 May (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Construction Advisory Committee, Applications, 1942 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Contracts, Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, General, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, General, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, General, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, General, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, General, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General, 1956-1957 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General, 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, 1960-1961 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, General, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, General (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1970 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General (1 of 3), 1971 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, General (2 of 3), 1971 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, General (3 of 3), 1971 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General, 1972-1973 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - “Defense Information Briefs for Members of Congress”, 1974 August (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Defense Supply Agency, Correspondence and Drafts, 1971-1975 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Discharge Information, 1967-1968 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Federal Academies, Press Release, 1976 March 12 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - First National Bank of Waco, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - “Foreign Military Sales and Military Assistance Facts”, Report, 1976 December (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 12438, Military Appropriations, Reports, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Hymn, “It was on a Friday Morning”, Clippings and Correspondence, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Marine Corps, Band Programs, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1950-1952 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1955-1965 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1968-1969 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1970-1972 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1973-1975 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Marine Corps, Correspondence, General, 1976-1978 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Military Academies, Clippings, Correspondence, and Press Releases, 1972-1975 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Navy, Child Support, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1951 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1952-1956 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1959-1961 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1962-1964 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1971-1972 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1973-1974 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Navy, Correspondence, General, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Navy, Doris Miller, Correspondence and Photographs, 1971-1977, undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Navy, Doris Miller, Screenplay, “A Man Called Doris”, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1936-1943 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1944-1953 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Navy, Naval Academy, Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Navy, Separation of Naval Personnel, Policy, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Navy, Thomas McClintock, Modern Pentathlon, Booklet and Statistics, 1974-1976 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Non-Commissioned Officers Association (NCOA), Special Report, 1975, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Office of Civil Defense, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Overseas Dependents Schools, Packet, “Overseas Employment Opportunities for Educators”, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Pentagon, Pamphlet, 1968 October (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Report, “Department of Defense Announces 371 Actions Affecting Installations and Activities”, 1970 March 6 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Report, “United States Military Posture for FY 1972”, 1971 March 9 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Report, “Using ACT on the Campus”, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Report to the President, “Progress in Ending the Draft and Achieving the All-Volunteer Force”, 1972 August (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Summer Hudson, Educational Services, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Tymco Air Sweeper Bid, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Uniformed Services University School of Medicine, Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Wool, “An Analysis of the Wool Fiber and Fabric Availability in the United States”, 1976 June (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Department of Energy, 1969-1978, undated; 4
    Subseries IV is one of the smallest sections in the collection. Materials pertain to the Department of Energy and the use of natural resources, specifically oil and coal. Most of the content dates back to President Jimmy Carter’s Administration in the late 1970s. Due to inflation and rising gas prices, government officials sought to identify alternative fuel sources.
    Folders in this subseries are arranged alphabetically according to the agency or material type. Overall, the materials are in good condition.
    - Analysis of Congressman Moore’s Amendment, 1978 July 14 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - “Energy Policy Monitor”, Reports, 1977 May-June (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Energy Supply Initiatives, Report, 1978 May 15 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, Printed Materials, 1976-1978 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Legal Documents and Statements, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Maps, “Total Interstate Energy Movement”, 1974-1977 (Box 149 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Oil and Gas in the 11th Congressional District, Data, circa 1969 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - President Carter’s Energy Plan, Reactions, 1977 April-May (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Printed Materials, 1978, undated (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Radioactive Waste, Fact Sheets and Maps, 1973-1978 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Texas Energy Development Fund Plan, Report, 1977 September (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - “Texas Energy Report”, 1977 February-June (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1950-1979, undated; 5
    Subseries V consists of materials pertaining to the Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (HEW). Due to the broad scope of the department, topics addressed in the materials vary widely including student loans, education reform, benefits, healthcare, welfare, and the integration of local area high schools. Reports and correspondence relating to the Food and Drug Administration, the Office of Education, and the Social Security Administration are prominently featured. Materials of a personal nature - including medical case files or Social Security cases - have been deaccessioned.
    - “A Report to the President and Congress on the Status of Health Professions Personnel in the United States”, 1978 August (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Adolescent Health Services Pregnancy Prevention and Care Act of 1978, Testimony, Secretary Joseph Califano, Jr., 1978 June 28 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Aid to Families with Dependent Children Work Incentive Program, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Aid to Families with Dependent Children Work Incentive Program, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - “American Education”, Publication, 1965 November (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Announcements, General, 1967-1975, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations Bills, 1977-1978 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Association of American Physicians and Surgeons (AAPS), Pamphlets, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Background Paper, “Social Security Benefits for Students”, 1977 May (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Baylor University, Immigration of Dr. Shim C. Park, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Brief, “National Nutritional Foods Association et al v. Food and Drug Administration et al”, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Appointments and Recommendations, 1956-1978 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Brownwood, Texas, Property Disbursement, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Budget, Fiscal Year 1979, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of Health Manpower, Health Professions Capitation Grants, Notification, 1978 September (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of Health Manpower, Notifications, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Bureau of Health Manpower, Nursing Capitation Grant Program, Notification, 1978 September (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Bureau of Health Manpower, Nursing Student Loan and Scholarship Programs, Notification, 1975 September (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Bureau of Health Manpower, Nursing Student Loan Program, Notification, 1977 August (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Bureau of Health Manpower, Nursing Student Loan Program, Notification, 1977 July (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Calvert, Texas, Integration, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Cancer, Correspondence, 1955-1968 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Chart, Proposed Reforms of Education Programs, undated (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Chart, Proposed Reforms of Health Service Programs, undated (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Children’s Bureau, “Infant Care”, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Clinical Laboratory Improvement Act of 1978, Correspondence (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1967-1978, undated (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Colleges and Universities, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1956-1978 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Colleges and Universities, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1956-1978 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Consumer Protection, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 5)